https://www.poolplaza.com/privacy-security

Pool Plaza.com
Search:
Search
Cart
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Compare
You have no items to compare.
Account
Wishlist
Log In
Menu
In-Ground Pools/Spas Pool Parts Pool Pumps Pump Parts ListPump Motors 1/2 Horsepower3/4 Horsepower1.0 Horsepower1-1/2 Horsepower2.0 Horsepower2-1/2 Horsepower3.0 HorsepowerAbove 3.0 HorsepowerCapacitorsMotor BearingsPool Filters Filter Parts ListReplacement Grids Grid AssembliesGrid SetsIndividual GridsReplacement CartridgesPool HeatersPool CleanersBackwash Valves & ValvesBaskets Skimmer BasketsPump BasketsLight Parts Parts ListReplacement Bulbs HalogenLEDQuartzStandardAdaptersGasketsTransformer BoxesChlorinator PartsSaltwater System PartsSkimmer Parts Skimmer Parts ListSkimmer BasketsSkimmer LidsMain Drain PartsO-ring and Gasket Kits Pump O-Ring Kits American Pumps O-Ring KitsAqua-Flo Pumps O-Ring KitsDoughboy Pumps O-Ring KitsHayward Pumps O-Ring KitsJacuzzi Pumps O-Ring KitsLeisure Bay Cyclone Pumps O-Ring KitsPentair PacFab Purex Pumps O-Ring KitsPremier Pumps O-Ring KitsZodiac (Polaris & Jandy) Pump O-Ring KitsSta-Rite Pumps O-Ring KitsFilter O-Ring KitsBackwash Valve O-Ring Kits American Backwash Valves O-Ring KitsAnthony Backwash Valves O-Ring KitsHayward Backwash Valves O-Ring KitsPentair PacFab Backwash Valves O-Ring KitsSta-Rite Backwash Valves O-Ring KitsChlorinator O-Ring KitsBackwash Valve O-Ring Kits American Backwash Valves O-Ring KitsAnthony Backwash Valves O-Ring KitsHayward Backwash Valves O-Ring KitsPentair PacFab Backwash Valves O-Ring KitsSta-Rite Backwash Valves O-Ring KitsReplacement Cells for Salt ChlorinatorsTimer & Freeze-guard Pool Pumps Residential PumpsFountain & Water FeaturesPool Cleaner Booster PumpsComplete Parts ListCommercial PumpsComplete Parts ListPond PumpsComplete Parts ListPump MotorsPool Cleaners Booster Pump Cleaners CleanersPartsPressure Cleaners CleanersPartsSuction Cleaners CleanersPartsRobotic Cleaners CleanersCommercialPartsPool Cleaner BagsPool Filters Cartridge Filters Complete Cartridge FiltersPartsReplacement CartridgesDE Filters Complete DE FiltersPartsReplacement GridsSand Filters Complete Sand FiltersPartsCommercial FiltersPool Heaters Propane HeatersPartsNatural Gas HeatersPartsCommercial ASME HeatersElectric HeatersSolar Heating Solar PanelsParts & KitsControlsSalt Water Systems Salt Water Chlorine GeneratorsReplacement CellsZinc AnodesPartsLights Pool LightsSpa Lights LightsParts GasketsAdaptersBulbsTransformer BoxesLensNichesFountain LightsFloating LightsReplacement Bulbs HalogenLEDQuartzStandardParts Parts ListAdaptersGasketsTransformer BoxesNichesBackwash Valves & Valves Backwash Valves Side MountTop MountCommercial ValvesActuatorsBall ValvesCheck ValvesDiverter ValvePartsBackyard Fun Floats Premium FloatsReclining & Adjustable LoungesInflatablesGamesToysNoodlesGrizzly CupsSwim & Dive Gear FinsSwim AidsFloating Lights & FountainsExercise & FitnessPool ArtKickboards & Surfer BoardsDiving Boards CompleteBoardsStandsSafety Equipment Rope & FloatsLife Savers Life RingsLife Hooks HooksPolesAlarms WristbandsAbove GroundGate/Door/WindowIn GroundPool Signs Novelty SignsSafety SignsPet RampsDrainsHandrails & Ladders HandrailsLaddersPartsOutdoor ShowersAutomatic Control System Electronic Controls Control UnitsPower/Load CentersSalt Systems Complete Salt SystemsReplacement CellsSolar Heating ControlsInterface/Remote ControlsAccessories CablesChemical DispensersUpgrade/Update KitsModulesOtherOutdoor/Mud BoxesRelaysSensorsTransformersParts Replacement CellsComplete Bundle KitsActuatorsTimers & Freeze-guards Timers Dual TimersSingle TimersWind-UpFreeze-guardsPartsAir SwitchesPool Maintenance & Cleaning Cleaning Equipment Residential Vacuums Vacuum HeadsHosesPartsBrushes & ScrubbersLeaf Traps Leaf TrapsLeaf Trap PartsPolesMaintenance KitsSkimmer BasketsSurface Skimmers & Leaf RakesCommercial Vacuums Vacuum HeadsHosesPartsBrushes & ScrubbersPolesMaintenance KitsSkimmer BasketsSurface Skimmers & Leaf RakesFlowmeters FlowmetersPartsThermometersTest Kits Test KitsTest StripsRefill ReagentsLubricantsFilter CleanersService ToolsStain RemoversHoses Backwash/Discharge HosesVacuum HosesPartsSpa WandsChemical Feeders/Chlorinators Inline Chemical FeedersOff-line Chemical FeedersFloating ChlorinatorsMineral/Nature2 SystemsPartsConstruction ElectricalHandrails & Ladders HandrailsLaddersPartsLight NichesMain Drains Complete Main DrainsPartsPaint & Coating Pool PaintPlumbing FittingsGlues & PrimersSkimmers & Skimmer Parts Complete SkimmersSkimmer Parts Skimmer Parts ListSkimmer BasketsSkimmer LidsStructural Repair Deck-O-SealPlaster & Tile RepairWaterfallsEyeballs/Return Jets Eyeballs/Return JetsPartsDiving Boards CompleteBoardsStandsPool Chemicals Step # 1 - SanitizersStep # 2 - ShockStep # 3 - Algae PreventativeAlgae KillersMetal, Scale & Stain InhibitorsClarifiersEnzymesCleaning ChemicalsTest Kits Test KitsTest StripsRefill ReagentsSalt Pool ChemicalsMineral Sanitizers/Nature2Closing & Start-Up KitsAccessoriesSpa BlowersOverstock/CloseoutCleanersPumpsFiltersHeatersPool ChemicalsPartsAbove Ground Pools Pool Pumps PumpsPump & Filter Combo Complete Pump & Filter ComboHosesComplete Parts ListPool Filters Cartridge Filters Complete FiltersReplacement CartridgesPartsDE Filters Complete FiltersReplacement GridsPartsSand Filters Complete FiltersPartsPump & Filter Combo Complete Pump & Filter ComboHosesPool Cleaners CleanersPartsPool Heaters Natural GasPropaneElectricPartsAutomatic Controls Electronic Controls Complete Control SystemsAccessoriesSalt Systems Complete Salt SystemsReplacement CellsPartsTimers & Freeze-guards TimersFreeze-guardsPartsSalt Systems Complete Salt SystemReplacement CellsZinc AnodesPool Lights LightsFloating Lights & FountainsPartsBackyard Fun Floats Premium FloatsReclining & Adjustable LoungesInflatablesGamesToysNoodlesSwim & Dive Gear FinsSwim AidsFloating Lights & FountainsExercise & FitnessPool ArtKickboards & Surfer BoardsPool Covers Solar Blankets Magni Clear Solar BlanketsBlue Solar BlanketsSolar Blanket
ReelsWinter Covers Mesh CoversSolid CoversAccessories Leaf NetsPool Cover PumpsPool Cover Air Pillows & Wall BagsPool Cover ClipsPool Cover DrainsCables Winches Patch KitsCover ReelsBackwash Valves & Valves Backwash Valves Side MountTop MountBall ValvesCheck ValvesDiverter ValvesPartsSafety Equipment AlarmsLife Savers Life RingsLife Hooks Life HooksPolesPool Signs Novelty SignsSafety SignsHandrails & Ladders LaddersPartsOutdoor ShowersParts Pool PumpsPump Motors 1/2 Horsepower3/4 Horsepower1.0 Horsepower1-1/2 Horsepower2.0 HorsepowerAbove 3.0 HorsepowerCapacitorsPool Filters Cartridge FiltersDE FiltersSand FiltersReplacement CartridgesReplacement GridsPool CleanersPool HeatersBackwash Valves & ValvesChemical FeedersPool Maintenance & Cleaning Cleaning Equipment Brushes & ScrubbersLeaf Eaters Leaf MasterLeaf TrapsPartsPolesSkimmer BasketsSurface Skimmers & Leaf RakesVacuums Vacuum HeadsHosesPartsFilter CleanersHoses Backwash/Discharge HosesVacuum HosesPartsLubricantsMaintenance KitsPolesService ToolsStain RemoversTest Kits Test KitsTest StripsRefill ReagentsThermometersRepair PatchChemical Feeders/Chlorinators Inline Chemical FeedersOffline Chemical FeedersFloating ChlorinatorsMineral SanitizersPartsPool ChemicalsCleanersPumpsFiltersHeatersPool ChemicalsPartsPortable Spas & Hot Tubs Jacuzzi Genuine Parts BlowersCircuit BoardsControl PanelsCovers & Cover Lifter PartsElectrical/ControllersFilters & CartridgesHeatersLightsPillowsPlumbingPumpsSanitizersSensorsSkimmersSkirt PanelsSundance Genuine Parts BlowersCircuit BoardsControl PanelsCovers & Cover Lifter PartsElectrical/ControllersFilters & CartridgesHeatersIn-Ground EquipmentLids/WeirsLightsPillowsPlumbingPumpsSanitizersSensorsSkirt PanelsSuntubTimersOther Spa & Hot Tubs Parts Air Controls & Air SwitchesAir BlowersCircuit BoardsControl PanelsCovers & Cover Lifters PartsElectrical/ControllersFilters & CartridgesHeatersJets & Jet PartsLightsPillowsPlumbingPumpsSanitizersSensorsSkimmersSpa Packs/Control and Equipment SystemStereo Components/Audio/VideoTimersFilters & CartridgesSpa StepsMaintenanceChemicals Bromine System Bromine FeedersBromine TabletsBromine ShockBalancersTestingNature II System Mineral StickSanitizersShocksBalancersTestingFrog System Mineral PadsBromine PadsShockBalancersTestingMineraluxe System Start-Up Kits3 Month KitSanitizer/Bromine TabsShock/Oxygen Pouch+Bromine ConeMineral CubesBalancersTestingSanitizersMineral SanitizersShockBalancersTest Kits & StripsFragranceJacuzzi ProClearSundance SunPurityAccessoriesAroma TherapyAccessories
NEW Spas & Hot Tubs
Jacuzzi Genuine Parts
Sundance Genuine Parts
Other Spa Brand Parts
Spa Filters
Pool/Spa Parts Waterway Skimmer PartsAladdin Skimmer PartsPentair Skimmer Parts Pentair Admiral Skimmer PartsPentair Bermuda Skimmer PartsPentair FAS100 Skimmer PartsHayward Skimmer Parts Hayward Skim Master 1070 Skimmer PartsHayward SP1075/SP1075T Skimmer PartsHayward SP1082/1083/1084/1085 Skimmer PartsHayward SP1096/1097/1098 Skimmer PartsHayward SP1091LX/1091WM Skimmer PartsSta-Rite Skimmer Parts Sta-Rite/SwimQuip U-3 Skimmer PartsSta-Rite Auto Surface Skimmer PartsBaker Skimmer Parts Baker Skimmer PartsJacuzzi Skimmer PartsCasa Newport Skimmer Replacement Lids
About Us
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Our Privacy and Security Pledge to You...
We are committed to respecting your privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of personally identifiable information you share with us.
In general, you can visit POOLplaza.com without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. That information is only required when you make a purchase.
To protect your privacy, we have adopted the following measures and policies to secure the information you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure:
All of your personal information stays private.
All order information is encrypted and transmitted to us over secure socket connections.
We do not retain your credit card information or store it on any of our computers.
We record your personal information only if you provide it to us when placing an order or expressing an interest in one of our products.
We use financial information only to bill you for products and services that you have purchased.
Once we receive the order, the information is stored on private servers not accessible from the internet.
We do not share this information with anyone.
We use cookies only to assist your shopping.
A "cookie" is a bit of info stored on your computer (not ours) which says "Hi,this is customer #1234".
When you are ready to place an order, the cookie will fill in the form with the address info you provide to us when you registered. This makes ordering much easier.
In short, we use your personal information only to serve you better. We want you to be comfortable contacting us or placing an order with us. We want you to be confident that placing an order
will not compromise your privacy in any way.
Sincerely,
POOLplaza.com
Site Map
Search Terms
Advanced Search
Orders and Returns
Contact Us
About Us
ABOUT POOLplaza
At POOLplaza, pool supplies are our only business. Our number one priority is to ensure that you, the customer, receive the highest quality and safest online shopping experience possible. It's been our dedication to providing exceptional customer service and to quality pool & spa equipment that has kept loyal customers returning to POOLplaza since 2002.
Simply put, POOLplaza is your one-stop online pool & spa supplies store.
Sign Up Now for Coupons & Discounts!
© 2020 Pool Plaza.com Store. All Rights Reserved. USA
Pool Plaza has a Shopper Approved rating of 4.7/5 based on 879 ratings and reviews.
